cuteonly.com 2019-12-10

# CuteOnly Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Effective: May 25, 2018

At CuteOnly, we are firmly committed to protecting your privacy. All personal information we collect from our customers is used only for the purpose of finding a perfect match. CuteOnly never sells or rents any personal information to any third parties. Below you will find what information we collect and how it is used and shared.

**BY USING THE SERVICES, YOU CONSENT TO THE COLLECTION, USE AND TRANSFER OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA FOR PROCESSING IN THE UNITED STATES AS DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.**

If you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that information we collect (including cookies and device data) will be processed and stored in the United States, a jurisdiction in which the data protection and privacy laws and principles, including your data subject rights, may not offer the same level of protection as those in the country/region where you reside or are a citizen.

**If you do not agree with any part of this Privacy Policy or our Terms, please do not access or continue to use any of the provided services or otherwise submit your Personal Data.**

  1. **Collection of Information**

We collect information about you when you create an account, visit our website and communicate with us. We also collect information, such as usage statistics, by using cookies and IP addresses.  IP is the series of numbers associated with the network you come from. This information does not disclose your personal details!

We need it to maintain our Web site and collect geographical statistics of our visitors. Cookies are small text files that websites place on your hard drive to identify you when you come back. We use cookies to deliver a content specific to your interests and to measure the effectiveness of CuteOnly advertisements. The use of cookies is a common practice on the Internet. You can disable all cookies through your browser settings.

  2. **Information We Ask You to Provide for Us**

Any identifying information you give us that is not visible to other visitors, such as your email address or surname, will be kept private. We never share this information with other companies without your permission. Whenever we ask you for information, we make it absolutely clear whether it is visible to other users or not. Some information you voluntarily provide, such as your personal description, age, anthropometric data, etc., is publicly visible unless you decide otherwise.

  3. **Use of Information**

We may use information about you to show and advertise your dating profile at CuteOnly websites, allow you to share information about your use of CuteOnly through other social media, to monitor and analyze usage statistics, to detect, investigate, and prevent fraudulent transactions, abuse, harassment or any other illegal or offensive activities, to protect the rights and safety of other CuteOnly users and to comply with applicable laws.

  4. **Your Correspondence**

All your interaction with other CuteOnly users as well as with the CuteOnly team is strictly confidential. It will never be used for purposes of research or advertising without your permission.

  5. **Non-Identifying Information**

Non-identifying information is used to help other users find your personal profile. We may also use this information in the future to research any improvements our service may need.

  6. **Financial Security**

Credit card information is processed by third party payment processing companies. Card numbers are transmitted directly to the banking networks for authorization. CuteOnly employees can’t have access to your card numbers. Sensitive information is encrypted with secure socket layer technology (SSL). SSL is what ensures complete security during the payment process.

  7. **Mailings**

CuteOnly uses your email address to send mailings from time to time. The purpose of mailings are:

    * Notifications on new messages sent to you by other community members
    * New member profiles, preferrably matching your criteria
    * To recover your password and other types of notifications
    * Other types of notifications, promotions and service announcements.
    * Our support team may contact you to assist you with your membership.
    * Our payment providers can use your email address to notify you on operations such as regular credit card charge.

To access or manage your subscriptions, please visit[ www.cuteonly.com/manage_subscriptions](https://www.cuteonly.com/manage_subscriptions)

The instructions to unsubscribe from our mailings are located in the bottom of the messages we send.  

  8. **Disclosure to The Residents of The European Economic Area  **

If you reside in the European Economic Area, you have certain rights to the Personal Data that we have collected about you, including Right of access to your Personal Data, Right to correction, Right to erasure, Right to restriction of processing, Right to data portability and Right to object. To exercise your rights to your Personal Data, please contact us through the address listed below. 

  9. **How to Contact Us**

If you have any further questions or concerns about our privacy policy contact us at 

**What's Next:**

* **CuteOnly Knowledge Base** \- Still have questions? Check out our FAQ's
* About CuteOnly
* CuteOnly Front Page
